Finding Aid for the Grand Ole Opry Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Grand Ole Opry Collection
1930s-1960s
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0178
2.94 linear_feet
Provenance
The Grand Ole Opry Collection was donated by Jesse Wills, president of National Life and Accident Insurance Company, the parent company of WSM, Inc. and the Grand Ole Opry. As president, Wills had access to a wide variety of material associated with country music in general and the Grand Ole Opry in particular. A collection of this material was donated by Jesse Wills in May of 1967 with additional items being given in July of 1968. The six boxes of material in the Grand Ole Opry Collection are complemented by the WSM Radio and TV collection, also donated to Vanderbilt Special Collections by Mr. Wills.
Scope and Content
The collection is composed of a wide variety of items of historical and musical interest. The correspondence dates roughly from the 1950s and 1960s and varies from fan letters to promotional campaigns. Clippings from the same time profile performers and personalities, the Opry, and the music industry in Nashville. The files include a representative collection of country and western magazines.
Songbooks comprise a significant proportion of the collection. Most of them date from the 1930s and 1940s. They include a good, though incomplete, collection of songbooks by Ernest Tubb. Many other performers are also represented.
Grand Ole Opry programs are available from 1961 to 1967 with some gaps. There are a large number of news releases under the title Here’s News About WSM’s Grand Ole Opry as well as news releases on a variety of performe.
Photographs highlight the Grand Ole Opry Collection. Pictures range from publicity shots to candid photographs of performances and tours. The cast of the Grand Ole Opry is recorded in pictures from several decades.
Unique items in the collection include the original layouts for some promotional materials and taped interviews with George D. Hay, Loretta Lynn, and Tex Ritter with Audie Murphy.
Incoming Correspondence listed in the original register and found missing in May of 1983. The original folder was probably marked “4-11 Correspondence-Incoming.” It was from Box 1 of the collection.
11 September 1966. Mrs. L.H. to Mr. Williams. Handwritten and signed
31 March 1928. Mrs. G. Banfield to WSM. Handwritten and signed. Fan letter.
28 October 1928. Thomas W. Bentley to Mr. Andrews. Handwritten and signed. Fan letter.
3 July 1961. Patsy Cline to Trudy [Stamper]. Handwritten and signed.
8 April 1960. Irene Hicks to Trudy [Stamper]. Handwritten and signed.
No date. Irene HIcks to ? Handwritten and signed. Written on a newspaper.
December, ? John Parrish and Babe Parrish to Tom Andrews. Handwritten and signed. Fan letter.
24 May 1965. John Zasoba to Mr. Williams. Handwritten and signed. Fan letter.
23 June-1965. Jimmy Pope to Grand Ole Opry. Handwritten and signed. Fan letter.
- Outgoing Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Les Barnard to Carl Simonson, 1945 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jack Harris to Reginald Clough, 1946 June 17 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hi Bramham to Sy Weintraub, 1955 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - W.D. Kilpatrick to “Mr. Fair Secretary”, 1958 January 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Royal McCullough to “Dee Jay”, 1958 September 24 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Trudy [Stamper] to Patsy [Cline?], 1960 November 28 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Robert E. Cooper to [Governor] Jimmy Davis [of Louisiana], 1961 October 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Trudy [Stamper] to “Friends”, 1963 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Grant Turner to "Loyal Opry Friends", 1964 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Trudy [Stamper] to Johnny Johnson, Trudy [Stamper] to Ron Kitson, Trudy [Stamper] to Heinz Rohde, Trudy [Stamper] to Johnny Russell, 1964 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Trudy Stamper to J.W. Pollie, Trudy Stamper to Frank C. Murray, 1964 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Trudy Stamper to Erling Norlev, 1964 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minnie Pearl - Invitation, [October], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Incoming Correspondence - General (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Blakely, Rodeo Rick. (To .Jo). 31 May 1964. Brissette, A.J. (To Trudy (Stamper]), 2 June 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clark, Ed. (To Jack [Harris, Assistant Genera) Manager, WSM]), N.D. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Day, Mark G. (To Len Hensel), 23 March 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Delehant, Jim. (To “Friends of Country Husic”), 24 September 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ferguson, Ken. (To Publicity Director), 31 March 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Governale, Marilyn. (To Robert Cooper), 22 April 1964; (To Dot Hamilton), 11 May 1964; (To Dot Hamilton), 25 May 1964; (To Dot Hamilton), 2 June 1964; (To Dot Hamilton), 28 August 1964; (To Dot Hamilton), 28 September 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Haller, Jay. (To Grand Ole Opry Stations), N.D. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hawkins, Charles S. (To Grand Ole Opry), 3 July 1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kirkpatrick, William D. (To Grand Ole Opry), 4 January 1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mathesen, Marelyn. (To William McDaniel), 11 November 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Reynolds, Dwight S. (To Robert Cooper), 19 February 1964; (To Rebert Cooper), 26 February 1964; (To Robert Cooper), 10 April 1964; (To All Kroger Grand Ole Opry Stations), 9 April 1964; (To Dot Hamilton), 24 April 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Simonson, Carl. (To Les Barnard), 1945 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Weintraub, Sy. (To William McDaniel), 26 November 1954; (To William McDaniel), 14 March 1955; (To Hi Bramham ), 9 June 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Williams, Cohen T. (To Trudy Siamper), 11 November 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Incoming Correspondence - Radio Stations (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CFGM - Richmond Hill, Ontario (Ron Kitsqn), 29 April 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CHAB - Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan (Ted Kelly), 21 May 1964, (Dick Bourne), 27 May 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CJBQ - Belleville, Ontario (Frank C. Murray), 5 May 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CJET - Smiths Falls, Ontario (J.W. Pollie), 20 April 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CKNX - (John Langridge), 1964? (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - KFHA - Tacoma, Washington (Johnny Johnson), 22 April 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - WCNO - Canton, Ohio (Frank Le Barba), 8 May 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - WDVA - Danville, Virginia (Ralph Hess, Jr.), 28 May 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - WOW - Omaha, Nebraska (Heinz Rohde), 24 April 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - WYAM - Birmingham, Alabama (David A. Binns), 29 May 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ? - Evansville, Indiana (Clyde M. Ricketts), 21 April 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Memoranda (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - To: Sponsors of Country Music Programs on WSM From: William R. McDaniel, Director of Public Relations, WSM Re: Fourth Annual National Disc Jockey Festival, 1955 November (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - To: Mr. Powell Stamper From: W.D. Kilpatrick Re: Agreements signed by Opry Artists for use of their pictures by National Life, 1957 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - To:Mr. Powell Stamper From: W.D. Kilpatrick Re: Agreements signed by Opry Artists for use of their pictures by Nat.ional Life, 1957 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - To: [Trudy] Stamper From: Dot Crowell Re: Personal appearances - Grand Ole Opry stars in 1960, 1961 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - To: ? From: Bob Cooper Re: Grand Ole Opry attendance in 1961, 1962 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- News Releases, Grand Ole Opry - History (Box 1, Folder 5)
- News Releases, Personalities (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bare, Bobby (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Boone, Pat (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Brasfield, Rod (telegram) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cline, Patsy (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cline, Patsy and Hamilton, George IV (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gibson, Don (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Jamup and Honey (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kincaid, Bradley (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Old Timer’s Quartet (Claude Sharpe, Fred Waller, Joseph MacPherson, and Luther Heatewole) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Reeves, Jim (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Russell, Don (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Beasley (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous News Releases, Synopses, Proposals, and Studies (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Clippings (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Personalities, A - H (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Personalities, I - P (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Personalities, Q - Z (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Personalities, Various (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Grand Ole Opry (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Music Industry, “Nashville Sound” (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Tabloids (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Greenville News, April 14. 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Music City News, Vol. 2, no. 5, November 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Pickin’ and Singin’ News, Vol. 2, no. 8 (April 23, 1954) Vol. 2, no. 9 (May 8, 1954) Vol. 2, no. 24, December 30, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Song Books
  - Roy Acuff and His Smoky Mountain Songs, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Roy Acuff Songbook (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Adventures of Tom Sawyer, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Arkansas (Arkie) Woodchopper: Square Dance Calls, 1940, 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Eddy Arnold Folio of Songs You Love, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gene Autry’s Sensational Collection of Famous Original Cowboy Songs and Mountain Ballads, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bailes Brothers Folio, no. 1, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Original Songs by Zeke Clements, The Dixie Yodeler, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Back in Baby’s Arms, recorded by Patsy Cline, 1963, sheet music (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Songs Cowboy Copas Sings, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Frank Crumit’s Book of Favorite Songs, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - John Daniel Quartet Grand Ole Opry Specials, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Joe Davis Entertainment and Minstrel Folio, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Delmore Brothers’ Folio of Native American Melodies, no. 1, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - “Little” Jimmy Dickens Folio Number 2, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lester Flatt and Earl Scruggs: Folk Music with an Overdrive, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Red Foley’s Cowboy Songs; Mountain Ballads (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Wally Fowler’s Oak Ridge Quartet Song Book Number One, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Wally Fowler: Nation Wide Hit Songs, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Pray, Pray, Pray for the U.S.A., by Wally Fowler, 1950, sheet music (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Haviland’s Good Ole Tunes, Number Two, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Paul Howard’s Cotton Pickin’ Songs, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Harmonies of the Hill Country Number Two, by Grandpa Jones (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fightin’ Son of a Gun, by Casper B. Kuhn, Sr., 1944, sheet music (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - George Morgan’s Songs for Home Folks, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Pie Plant Pete and Bashful Joe’s Favorite Old Time Songs, Song Book Number Three, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Radio Rube’s Song Book, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Claude Sharpe’s Old Hickory Quartet Song Book, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Shelton Brothers’ Collection of Record Songs Hits, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Short Brothers’ Radio Song Folio Number One, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Asher Sizemore and LIttle Jimmie’s Family Circle Songs, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tony, Juanita and Buddys’s Album of Mountain and Cowboy Songs, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ernest Tubb Radio Song Book Number One, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ernest Tubb Radio Song Book Number Two, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ernest Tubb Radio Song Book Number Three, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ernest Tubb Folio of Recorded Hits Number Two, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ernest Tubb Folio of Recorded Hits Number Three, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ernest Tubb Folio of Recorded Hits Number Four, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Mountain Broadcast Prairie Recorder, no. 1, September 1944 Sect one of two sections on Ernest Tubb (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ernest Tubb Song Folio of Sensational Successes Number One, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ernest Tubb Song Folio of Sensational Successes Number Two, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Tubb Song Folio of Sensational Successes Number Three, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ernest Tubb Song Folio Sensational Successes Number Four, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Justin Tubb Song Folio of Recorded Hits Number One, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Warner Brothers Song Folio, Second Edition, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - York Brothers Famous Folio of Songs to Remember, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - York Brothers Famous Folio of Songs to Remember 1943, copy 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - I’m A Soldier for Jesus,undated, by the York Brothers, sheet music (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Grand Ole Opry Programs (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - August 19, 1961 - October 7, 19t1; October 21, 1961 - December 30, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - January 13, 1962 - March 3, 1962; March 17, 1962 - December 29, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Grand Ole Opry Programs (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - January 5, 1963 - December 28, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - January 4, 1964 - February 8, 1964; February 22, 1964 - March 7, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - March 21, 1964; April 11, 1964 - June 27, 1964; July 11, 1964 - December 26, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Grand Ole Opry Programs (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - January 9, 1965 - January 30, 1965; February 13, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - April 24, 1965 - October 9, 1965; October 23, 1965 - November 6, 1965; November 27, 1965 - December 18, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - January 8, 1966; February 5, 1966 - February 12, 1966; March 19, 1966 - April 9, 1966; May 21, 1966 - June 18, 1966; July 9, 1966 - November 26, 1966; December 10, 1966 - April 29, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Here’s News About WSM’s Grand Ole Opry, all copies, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Marketing Presentations (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Schlappi, Elizabeth. Roy Acuff and His Smoky Mountain Boys, Discography, Country Research Series, Disc Collector #23. Cheswold, Delaware: Disc Collector Publications, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Schlappi, Elizabeth. Alphabetical List of Roy Acuff’s Recordings as of September ’66. Manuscript. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Schlappi. Elizabeth. Alphabetical List of Roy Acuff’s Recordings (As of Mid-1970). Manuscript, xeroxed. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Souvenir Books (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - All Star Scrapbook (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cousin Jody and Odie Photo Album, 195? (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Country and Western Scrapbook, 12 edition, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Country and Western Show Souvenir Book, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Country and Western Souvenir Picture Album, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Country Music Picture Album, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lester Flatt [and] Earl Scruggs and the Foggy Mountain Boys Radio and TV Album and Songbook, no. 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lester Flatt & Ecrl Scruggs Picture Album and Song Book, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lester Flatt & Earl Scruggs, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lester Flatt & Earl Scruggs and the Foggy Mountain Boys, Picture Album - Song Book, 1959? (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Grand Ole Opry - Souvenir Books (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Backstage at WSM’s Grand Ole Opry, [1961?], 2 copies (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Blue Jeans and Calico - Opry, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Grand Ole Opry Souvenir Program, 195? (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Grand Ole Opry WSM Picture - History Book, 50th Anniversary Issue Volume 6, Edition 1, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Martha White - Pet Milk Grand Ole Opry Show, Souvenir Program Picture Album, 1960? (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Purina’s Grand Ole Opry and Checkerboard Fun-Fest Souvenir Album, 1945? (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - WSM’s Official Grand Ole Opry History-Picture Book, Vol. 1, no. 1, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - WSM’s Official Grand Ole Opry History-Picture Book, Vol. 1, no. 3, 1961? (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - WSM Grand Ole Opry Official Opry History-Picture Book, Vol. 3 edition 1, l966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Souvenir Books (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hillbilly and Western Scrapbook, 1957 edition (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Parade of Stars Souvenir Scrapbook, 1958? (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The “Pop” Scrapbook, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - George Morgan, Grand Ole Opry (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Pictures, Biographies, Current Recordings of Your Favorite countr, and Hillbilly Recording Artists [Capitol Records], 1954? (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - RCA Victor Country and Western Caravan Special Recording Artists, 1953? (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Marty Robbins, Mr. Teardrop, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook of Hillbilly & Western Stars, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Souvenir Picture Album, Special Fair Edition, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - A Story of the Grand Ole Opry by George D. Hay, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Porter Wagoner Show, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Porter Wagoner Show, Vol. 2, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Porter Wagoner Show, Vol. 3, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Wilburn Brothers Show, Folio no. 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Programs and Souvenir Books (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Grand Ole Opry (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - This is Grand Ole Opry Day at the Ill. State Fair, August 15. 1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - The Washington Coliseum [Washington, D.C.], Saturday, October 3 [1964? (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Kroger Presents Grand Ole Opry Country and Folk Music Fall Festival, Souvenir Program Cobo Hall, Detroit Michigan, Oct. 20, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Magazines
  - Billboard, The World of Country Music, 1963-1964 edition., November 2, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Country and Western Jamboree, January 1957 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Country and Western Jamboree, June 1957 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Country and Western Jamboree, July 1957 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Country and Western Jamboree, 1959 Yearbook (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Country Music Life, December 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Country Music Life, February 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Country Music Life, March 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Country Music Life, May 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Country Music Life, August 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Country Music Review, September 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Country Music World and Yearbook, Volume 1, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Country Song Roundup, Vol. 18, no. 95, August 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Country Song Roundup, Vol. 18, no. 96, October 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Country Song Roundup, Vol. 18, no. 97, December 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Country Song Roundup, Vol. 19, no. 99, April 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Country Song Roundup, Vol. 19., no. 102, October 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Country Song Roundup Annual, Winter 1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cowboy Songs, no. 54 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Folk and Country Songs, Vol. 3, no. 12, July 1958 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - International Musician, Vol. 62, no. 10, April 1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Music Reporter, Vol. 8, no. 5, August 31, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Music Reporter, Vol. 8, no. 14, November 2, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Popular Country Stars, Vol. 1, no. 1, October 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Rustic Rhythm, Vol. 1, no. 6, September 1957 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sing Out!, Vol. 13, no. 1, February - March 1963 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sound Format, Vol. 2, no. 8, June 30, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Tennessee Folklore Society Bulletin, Vol. 27, no. 1, March 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Trail, Vol. 1, no. 3, May - June 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Trail, Vol. 1, no. 7, January - February 1959 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Photographs
  - Pat Boone (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Margie Bowes (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Composite, three frames: Rod Brasfield, Red Foley, Rod Brasfield (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Rod Brasfield-jumping (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - Rod Brasfield-with lamp (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Rod Brasfield-with pipe (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 6)
  - Rod Brasfield-lighting cigarette with lamp (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 7)
  - Carnegie Hall, November 1961 - People viewing poster (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 8)
  - Carnegie Hall, November 1961 Front row: Vito Pellettieri (Opry stage manager); Minnie Pearl; Mayor Wagner of New York City; Grandpa Jones Back row: Faron Young; Bill Williams, journalist; Patsy Cline; unknown man, unknown woman, unknown man, Bill Monroe (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 9)
  - Carnegie Hall, November 1961 Grandpa Jones, Minnie Pearl, Faron Young, Bill Monroe, Patsy Cline Woolworth Building in background (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 10)
  - Starting lower left, going clockwise: Grandpa Jones, Patsy Cline, MInnie Pearl, Jim Reeves, Faron Young, and Bill Monroe. New York Airport (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 11)
  - CarRegie Hall, November 1961. Patrons for the Grand Ole Opry Show in lobby (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 12)
  - Carnegie Hall, November 1961. Marty Robbins performing (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 13)
  - Patsy Cline. Autographed. (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 14)
  - Patsy Cline (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 15)
  - Grave marker for Patsy Cline, c., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 16)
  - Coca-Cola promotion - Young people holding up bottles of Coke, 12 May 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 17)
  - Stoney Cooper, Wilma Lee Cooper, Johnny Clark, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 18)
  - Stoney Cooper, Johnny Clark, and Wilma Lee Cooper, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 19)
  - Dill, Devine, [Pete] Drake, Harris. [Wake Island Post Office], 195? (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 20)
  - Composite, three frames: Red Foley in all three (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 21)
  - Composite, six frames: Top row: Red Foley; Minnie Pearl; Red Roley, Minnie Pearl, and Rod Brasfield Bottom Row: unknown guitarist, Red Foley; Red Foley; Rod Brasfield (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 22)
  - Hank Garland-guitar, Floyd “Lightnin”’ Chance-bass, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 23)
  - Hank Garland-guitar, Margie Bowes-singing (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 24)
  - “Purina’s Grand Ole Opry,” Picture of Grand Ole Opry cast 2 copies (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 25)
  - Grand Ole Opry cast, 194? (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 26)
  - Grand Ole Opry cast, composite, postcard (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 27)
  - “Stars of the Grand Ole Opry,” composite of 48 portraits (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 28)
  - Crowd lined up for Opry. Nashville, Tennessee. Ryman Auditorium in background., 195? (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 29)
  - Crowd lined up for Opry. Nashville, Tennessee, in front of Ryman Auditorium. Postcard. (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 30)
  - Gully Jumpers (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 31)
  - Unknown-guitar, Hawkshaw Hawkins,unknown-bass (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 32)
  - At microphone: Faron Young, T. Tommy Cutrer Middle row: Gordon Stoker(Jordanaire), Neil Matthews(Jordanaire, [Hoyt Hawkins](Jordanaire), unidentified Jordanaire, Chet Atkins-guitar, Lew Childre-dobro, unidentified man Back row: 4 unknown men in plaid shirts [The Deputies, Faron Young’s band?] (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 33)
  - The La Dell Sisters, 1958? (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 34)
  - Uncle Dave Macon (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 35)
  - Unknown woman, Ron Piggott, Minnie Pearl, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 36)
  - Minnie Pearl, Rod Brasfield as Santa Claus (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 37)
  - Composite, six frames. Prince Albert Show, [194?] Minnie Pearl; Minnie Pearl; Rod Brasfield; Minnie Pearl; Minnie Pearl; Red Foley (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 38)
  - Pet Milk Promotion, children at dispenser (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 39)
  - Ray Pillow-guitar, T. Tommy Cutrer, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 40)
  - 4 unknown men, Grant Turner, Cowboy Copas, unknown man, Don Helms, Rusty Gabbard-seated with guitar, Jack Stapp (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 41)
  - Jim Reeves (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 42)
  - Marty Robbins, unknown man, T. Tommy Cutrer (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 43)
  - Sarah and Sally [Edna Wilson and Margaret Waters, mid-1930s] (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 44)
  - Claude Sharpe’s Old Hickory Singers [1952]. Two frames (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 45)
  - Stony Mountain Cloggers (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 46)
  - Female members of Stony Mountain Cloggers (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 47)
  - Cliff Thomas, 4 Michigan beauty queens, T. Tommy Cutrer (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 48)
  - Uncle Jimmy Thompson, c. 1925 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 49)
  - Unknown man-ukelele, Hank Snow, Ernest Tubb (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 50)
  - Ernest Tubb (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 51)
  - Ernest Tubb (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 52)
  - “Justin Tubb and His Pony” (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 53)
  - Kitty Wells (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 54)
  - Slim Whitman, Tom Perryman (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 55)